Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Athletics, Communications, Records SC0367
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, 1970-1995; Accession ARCH-1995-170
  - Men's Basketball vs. S. Utah 1/2/1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball vs. CS Northridge 1/4/1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball at OSU 1/9/1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball at Oregon 1/11/1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Men's Basketball vs. CAL 1/15/1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball vs. USC 1/23/1992 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Men's Basketball vs. UCLA 1/25/1992 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Men's Basketball at WSU 1/30/1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Men's Basketball at UW 2/2/1992 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Arizona 2/6/1992 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Men's Basketball vs. ASU 2/8/1992 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Men's Basketball at Notre Dame 2/11/1992 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Men's Basketball at CAL 2/15/1992 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Men's Basketball at UCLA 2/20/1992 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Men's Basketball at USC 2/22/1992 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Men's Basketball vs. UW 2/27/1992 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Men's Basketball vs. WSU 3/1/1992 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Men's Basketball at ASU 3/5/1992 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Men's Basketball at Arizona 3/7/1992 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Oregon 3/12/1992 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Men's Basketball vs. OSU 3/14/1992 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Men's Basketball NCAA 1992 vs. Alabama at Cincinnati 3/19/1992 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Australian All Stars 11/9/1991 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Women's Basketball at Georgia 11/22/1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball at Notre Dame 11/24/1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Women's Basketball 7up/UNLV Desert Classic 11/29-30/1991 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Long Beach 12/7/1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Tennessee 12/14/1991 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Women's Basketball Cardinal Classic 12/19-20/1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Women's Basketball vs. San Diego 12/28/1991 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Santa Clara 1/3/1992 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Women's Basketball at CAL 1/10/1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Women's Basketball vs. USC 1/16/1992 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Women's Basketball vs. UCLA 1/18/1992 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Women's Basketball at WSU 1/23/1992 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Women's Basketball at Washington 1/25/1992 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Arizona 1/30/1992 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Women's Basketball vs. ASU 2/1/1992 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Women's Basketball at Oregon St. 2/6/1992 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Women's Basketball at Oregon 2/8/1992 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Women's Basketball at UCLA 2/14/1992 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Women's Basketball at USC 2/16/1992 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Women's Basketball vs. UW 2/20/1992 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Women's Basketball vs. WSU 2/22/1992 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Women's Basketball at ASU 2/27/1992 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Women's Basketball at Arizona 2/29/1992 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Oregon 3/5/1992 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Women's Basketball vs. OSU 3/7/1992 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Women's Basketball vs. CAL 3/13/1992 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Women's Basketball NCAA 2nd Rd. vs. UCSB 3/21/1992 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Stanford Volunteers for Youth (Photographic contacts) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Weightlifting Contacts (Photographic) (also Andy Geiger mugs) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Paul Wiggin Contacts (Photographic) 1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - 1975 Spring Football Prospectus (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1976 Spring Football Prospectus (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - 1977 Spring Football Prospectus (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - 1978 Spring Football Prospectus (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - 1979 Spring Football Prospectus (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - 1980 Spring Football Prospectus (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 1981 Spring Football Prospectus (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - 1982 Spring Football Prospectus (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - 1983 Spring Football Prospectus (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - 1984 Spring Football Prospectus (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 1985 Spring Football Prospectus (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - 1986 Spring Football Prospectus (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - 1987 Spring Football Prospectus (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - 1990 Spring Football Prospectus (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Football vs. UW 9/7/1991 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Football at Arizona 9/14/1991 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Football vs. Colorado 9/28/1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Football vs. Notre Dame 10/5/1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Football vs. Cornell 10/12/1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Football at USC 10/19/1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Football vs. Oregon State 10/26/1991 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Football at Oregon 11/2/1991 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Football vs. UCLA 11/9/1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Football at WSU 11/19/1991 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Football vs. CAL 11/23/1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Stanford Band Contacts (Photographic) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball Contacts (Photographic) (from 1983-1991) (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball Contacts (Photographic) 1983-1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Baseball Contacts (Photographic) 1983-1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Cross Country Contacts (Photographic) 1977-1990 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Fencing Contacts (Photographic) 1978-1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Field Hockey Contacts (Photographic) 1978-1987 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Football Contacts (Photographic) 1984 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Golf Contacts (Photographic)- Men's and Women's 1975-89 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Golf Course Contacts (Photographic) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Golf Tournaments Contacts (Photographic) (Watson Pro-Am, Cardinal Club Celeb) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Gymnastics Contacts (Photographic)- Men's and Women's 1977-1990 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Contacts (Photographic) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Olympic Contacts (Photographic) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Physical Education Class Contacts (Photographic) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Press Box Contacts (Photographic) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Rugby Contacts (Photographic) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Soccer Contacts (Photographic) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Women's Softball Contacts (Photographic) 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Staff Contacts (Photographic) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Swimming Contacts (Photographic)- Men's and Women's 1978-1989 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Men's Tennis Contacts (Photographic) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Women's Tennis Contacts (Photographic) 1980-91 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Men's and Women's Track Contacts (Photographic) 1972-92 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Men's Volleyball Contacts (Photographic) 1978-91 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Women's Volleyball Contacts (Photographic) 1981-1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Water Polo Contacts (Photographic) 1977-90 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Wrestling Contacts (Photographic) 1982-1989 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Basketball Players; H. Dalmar (slides) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Football Coaches and Staff (slides) (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Football Games 1972-1973 (slides) (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Football Games 1974-1975 (slides) (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Football Games and individuals (slides) (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Football players 1970-1976 (slides) (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Football players 1970-1976 (slides) (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Football players 1981-1983: Andrew - Dillard (slides) (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Football players 1981-1983: Dykstra - Mitchel (slides) (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Football players 1981-1983: Moore - Wyman (slides) (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Football players 1987: Anderson - Hawkins (slides) (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Football players 1987: Hinckley - Newton (slides) (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Football players 1987: Nichols - Taylor (slides) (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Football players 1987: Teeuws - Zentner and coach (slides) (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous - Dollies, Super Bowl, memorabilia, campus shots (slides) (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Clippings, 1994-1995; Accession ARCH-1996-016
  - Football clippings, 1994 (I) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Football clippings, 1994 (II) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Football clippings, 1995, and Coach Willingham clippings (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Baseball clippings, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball clippings, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball clippings, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Sports clippings, Crew to Tennis, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Sports clippings, Track to Wrestling, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Additional Records, 1945-1993; Accession ARCH-1996-062
  - Men's basketball vs. Puget Sound, 12/2/1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball at San Jose State 12/3/1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball at Virginia 12/5/1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Sac State 12/12/1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Howard Univ. 12/19/1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Men's Basketball at Maui Invite 12/21/23/1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball hosts Fry's Invite 12/28-29/1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Santa Clara 1/2/1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball vs. OSU 1/7/1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball vs. ORE. 1/9/1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Notre Dame 1/12/1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Men's Basketball at Cal 1/14/1993 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Men's Basketball at UCLA 1/21/1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Men's Basketball at USC 1/23/1993 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Men's Basketball vs. WSU 1/28/1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Men's Basketball vs. WASH. 1/30/1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Men's Basketball at Arizona 2/4/1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Men's Basketball at ASU 2/6/1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Men's Basketball vs. CAL 2/14/1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Men's Basketball vs. UCLA 2/18/1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Men's Basketball vs. USC 2/20/1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Men's Basketball at WASH. 2/25/1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Men's Basketball at WSU 2/27/1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Men's Basketball vs. ASU 3/4/1993 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Men's Basketball vs. Arizona 3/7/1993 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Men's Basketball at Oregon 3/11/1993 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Men's Basketball at OSU 3/13/1993 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Belgium 11/20/1992 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Women's Basketball at Hawaii Tourney 12/4-6/1992 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Texas Tech 12/1/1992 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Women's Basketball vs. UCSB 12/13/1992 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Women's Basketball at TN 12/21/1992 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Women's Basketball at Long Beach 12/30/1992 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Women's Basketball at San Diego 1/2/1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Women's Basketball vs. TEXAS 1/5/1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball at OSU 1/7/1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Women's Basketball at Oregon 1/9/1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Women's Basketball vs. CAL 1/15/1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Women's Basketball at USC 1/18/1993 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Women's Basketball vs. UCLA 1/21/1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Women's Basketball USC 1/23/1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Women's Basketball at WSU 1/28/1993 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Women's Basketball at WASH 1/30/1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Arizona 2/4/1993 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Women's Basketball vs. ASU 2/6/1993 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Women's Basketball at CAL 2/12/1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Women's Basketball at UCLA 2/18/1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Women's Basketball at Conn. 2/20/1993 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Women's Basketball vs. WASH 2/25/1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Women's Basketball vs. WSU 2/27/1993 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Women's Basketball at ASU 3/4/1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Women's Basketball at Arizona 3/6/1993 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Oregon 3/11/1993 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Women's Basketball vs. OSU 3/13/1993 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Women's Basketball NCAA 2nd Round 3/20/1993 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Women's Basketball Regional Semifinal -- COLORADO (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Football: Pigskin Classic 8/26/1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Football vs. Oregon 9/12/1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Football vs. Northwestern, 9/19/1992 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Football vs. San Jose State 9/26/1992 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Football at Notre Dame 10/3/1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Football at UCLA 10/10/1992 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Football vs. Arizona 10/17/1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Football at Oregon State 10/24/1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Football at Washington, 10/31/1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Football vs. USC 11/7/1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Football vs. Washington St. 11/4/1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Football at CAL 11/21/1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bio Sheets & Photo of Alf Brandin, Raymond Todd, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Football Photos-- Games 1964, 68 & undated. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 1972 Rose Bowl-- photos (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Football Team photos 1941-65 & undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Football Team lists (separated from photos) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Football Coaches Photos (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Football Photos (Players-- identified A-M) [Jerry Beatie, Chris Burford, John Clark, Jim Castagnoli, Jack Douglas, Hyland, Mike Hibler, Dean Hinshaw, Stan Lindskog, Rick McMillen] (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Football Photos (Players-- identified N-Z) [Bob Nichols, Dick Norman, Al Norgard, Gary Pettigrew, Dick Ragsdale, Chuck Shea, Russ Steele, Danny Spence, John Stewart, Ted Tanner, Gary Van Calder, Lou Valli, Tom Walsh] (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Football Photos (Players-- unidentified) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Football Photos Misc. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Dept. photos, 1945-ca 1980 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Basketball Coaches Photos (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Track Coaches Photos (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Misc. Sports, Coaches Photos (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Baseball - Photos (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Basketball - Photos (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Golf Photos (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Gymnastic Photos (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Misc. Sports -- Photos (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Tennis Photos (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Track Photos (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Wrestling & Boxing Photos 1967 & Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Misc. Athletic photos (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Misc. Athletics slides (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Buildings -- Stanford Campus (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Stanford Band Photos 1971 & Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Dick & Karen Berg -- photos (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Stanford dollies 1966-1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Stanford dollies Photos 1973-80 & Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Stanford dollies Slides 1972-1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Stanford dollies Clippings (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Football Clippings (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook of Clippings: Football, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Additional Records, 1954-1994; Accession ARCH-1996-204
  - Three scrapbooks of clippings on football, 1993 and, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
  - One scrapbook of clippings on basketball, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - One scrapbook of clippings on baseball, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - One scrapbook of clippings on all sports, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - One scrapbook of clippings on miscellaneous sports, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - One scrapbook of clippings on the World Cup (soccer), 1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - One notebook containing the Stanford Buck Club Bulletin, January 1954 - May 1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Coaches and administrators, photoprints (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Color negatives, miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Color negatives, women's basketball Stanford v. Tennessee (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Football 1982/1983 season, color slides and black and white prints (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Football 1983/1984 season, color slides (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Football 1984/85 season, color slides (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Football 1986/1987 season, color slides (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Football players, black and white contact sheets (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous football, color slides (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Tennis and miscellaneous sports, color slides and a few color prints (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Women athletes, unknown sport, black and white contact sheets (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Women's basketball 1987 team, color photoprints (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Boxed color slides: 1981 football mug shots; 1982 football mug shots; women's basketball 1989-1990; Dick Gould; Steve Raczyask; campus shots (Box 5)
  - Boxed color slides: men's basketball; women's basketball 1985; miscellaneous football; miscellaneous sports and campus shots (Box 6)
- Additional Records, 1930-1996; Accession ARCH-1998-193
  - Baseball 1978-79, 1981-1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Men's cross country pre-1982, 1982-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Women's cross country 1978-79, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Men's crew 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Women's crew 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Fencing pre-1981, 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Field hockey pre-1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Men's golf 1981, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Women's golf pre-1983, 1983-1987 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Men's gymnastics pre-1981, 1982-1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Women's gymnastics pre-1980, 1981-1987 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Men's soccer 1981, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Women's soccer 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Women's softball 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Women's swimming pre-1980, 1980-1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Men's swimming 1982, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Men's tennis pre-1980, 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Men's tennis 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Women's tennis 1977, 1979-1987 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Men's and women's track 1983-1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Men's volleyball 1976, 1983-1986 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Water polo pre-1978, 1978-1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Wrestling pre-1980, 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Men's basketball game files, Nov. 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Men's basketball 1976-82 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Women's basketball 1981-83 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Women's basketball game files 1993-1995 (Box 6)
  - Binder of records re men's golf 1930s-1950s (Box 7)
  - Binders of clippings and press releases re men's and women's basketball, 1995-96 (Box 7)
  - Binder of records re tennis and golf 1950s (Box 8)
  - Binders of clippings and press releases re sports other than basketball, 1995-96 (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous clippings re football (Box 8)
- Additional Records, 1987-1998; Accession ARCH-1999-273
  - Football at Washington 9/14/1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Football vs. San Jose State 9/11/1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Football vs. Colorado 9/18/1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Football vs. UCLA 9/25/1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Football vs. Notre Dame 10/2/1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Football at Arizona 10/16/1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Football vs. ASU 10/23/1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Football vs. Oregon State 10/30/1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Football at USC 11/6/1993 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Football at Oregon 11/13/1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Football vs. CAL 11/20/1993 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Football at Northwestern 9/10/1994 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Football vs. San Jose State 9/17/1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Football vs. Arizona 9/24/1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Football at Notre Dame 10/1/1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Football at ASU 10/8/1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Football vs. USC 10/15/1994 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Football at Oregon State 10/22/1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Football at UCLA 10/29/1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Football vs. Washington 11/5/1994 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Football vs. Oregon 11/12/1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Football at CAL 11/19/1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Football at San Jose State 9/2/1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Football at Utah 9/9/1995 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Football vs. Wisconsin 9/16/1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Football at Oregon 9/23/1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Football at ASU 10/7/1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Football vs. Washington 10/14/1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Football vs. UCLA 10/21/1995 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Football vs. Oregon State 10/28/1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Football Clippings, 1/1996 to 8/1996 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Football Clippings, 9/1996 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Football Clippings, 9/1996 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Football Clippings, 10/1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Football Clippings, 11/1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Football Clippings, 11/1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Football Clippings, 12/1996 to 4/1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Women's Basketball vs. German National Team 11/10/1990 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Women's Basketball at Tennessee 11/25/1990 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Women's Basketball at CS Long Beach 11/30/1990 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Notre Dame 12/2/1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Women's Basketball at Colorado 12/6/1990 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Women's Basketball at Utah 12/8/1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Cardinal Classic--Women's Basketball 12/21-22/1990 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Women's Basketball at Super Shootout at Hilton Head 12/29-30/1990 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Oregon State 1/3/1991 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Oregon 1/5/1991 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Women's Basketball at Washington 1/11/1991 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Women's Basketball at WSU 1/13/1991 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Women's Basketball vs. UCLA 1/17/1991 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Women's Basketball vs. USC 1/19/1991 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Women's Basketball at Arizona 1/24/1991 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Women's Basketball vs. CAL 2/1/1991 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Women's Basketball vs. UNLV 2/2/1991 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Women's Basketball vs. WSU 2/7/1991 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Washington 2/9/1991 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Women's Basketball at USC 2/15/1991 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Women's Basketball at UCLA 2/17/1991 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Arizona State 2/21/1991 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Arizona 2/23/1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Women's Basketball at CAL 3/1/1991 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball at Oregon 3/7/1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Women's Basketball at Oregon State 3/9/1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Women's Basketball at West Regional vs. Washington 3/31/1991 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Women's Basketball at West Regional vs. Georgia 3/23/1991 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Women's Basketball--Fry's/Cardinal Invite 12/18-19/1992 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - USA Women's Basketball vs. Peninsula All-Stars 6/19/1993 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Australian Institute of Sport 11/24/1993 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Women's Basketball at Texas Tech 11/27/1993 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Women's Basketball at Utah 11/29/1993 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Tennessee 12/3/1993 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Long Beach State 12/8/1993 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Women's Basketball Tournament 12/17-18/1993 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Women's Basketball vs. UCONN 12/28/1993 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Women's Basketball vs. UNLV 12/30/1993 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Women's Basketball at Santa Clara 1/3/1994 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Women's Basketball at Washington 1/6/1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Women's Basketball at WSU 1/8/1994 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Women's Basketball vs. ASU 1/13/1994 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Arizona 1/15/1994 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Women's Basketball at CAL 1/21/1994 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Women's Basketball at UCLA 1/28/1994 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Women's Basketball at USC 1/30/1994 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Women's Basketball at Oregon 2/3/1994 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Women's Basketball vs. OSU 2/5/1994 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Women's Basketball at Arizona 2/10/1994 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Women's Basketball at ASU 2/13/1994 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Women's Basketball vs. CAL 2/18/1994 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Women's Basketball vs. USC 2/24/1994 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Women's Basketball vs. UCLA 2/26/1994 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Women's Basketball at OSU 3/3/1994 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Women's Basketball at Oregon 3/5/1994 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Women's Basketball vs. WSU 3/10/1994 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Women's Basketball vs. Washington 3/12/1994 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Women's Basketball Box Scores, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Women's Basketball Box Scores, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 4)